russian-women.net 2005-02-06

# Russian women - Privacy Statement

[26 new brides](http://www.russian-women.net/new_profiles_today.shtml) added Sunday February 6 2005 at 01:10 GMT: [Click here!](http://www.russian-women.net/new_profiles_today_thumbnailed.shtml)   
[17 previous personals profiles photos](http://www.russian-women.net/updated_photos_today.shtml) updated today. [Click here for thumbs!](http://www.russian-women.net/updated_photos_today_thumbnailed.shtml)   
[Photos updated last week - links with thumbs (may be huge page to load!)](http://www.russian-women.net/updated_photos_thumbnailed_weekly.shtml)   
Currently there are **28854** Russian personals in [**OUR Dating Album**](http://www.russian-women.net/album).   And **23851** previously listed women are no longer available.  **Approaching Valentine's Day on February 14th - show her that you care about her, send her**[ **GIFTS and FLOWERS**](http://www.russian-women.net/gifts.shtml) !    

Since we were founded, The Russian Women Network has tried to help its customers retain their privacy while they take advantage of all our site has to offer. We are committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful, safe, online experience that you can get anywhere. If you have questions about this, please write us at [ privacy@russian-women.net](mailto:privacy@russian-women.net?subject=%22Re:Privacy%22)

## Privacy Principles

Because your privacy is important to us, we will operate by the following principles. Users seeking additional information regarding the principles should consult the Frequently Asked Questions section accompanying this statement. 

The Russian Women Network explicitly asks you for general contact information when it needs it to personally identify you ("Personal Information"). You may update this information at any time, from within our [Account Infromation Page](http://www.russian-women.net/csedit.shtml) by signing in and clicking the **[Edit Your Profile]** button. 

The Russian Women Network use your Personal Information to operate The Russian Women Network site and services and to communicate with you regarding your accounts with The Russian Women Network. 

The Russian Women Network may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

  * conform to the edicts of the law; 
  * protect and defend the rights or property of The Russian Women Network, the site or the users of The Russian Women Network; 
  * act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The Russian Women Network, the site or the public. 

As part of your participation in any of The Russian Women Network services, The Russian Women Network allows you to elect to receive or not receive certain information and email from The Russian Women Network or its service partners.  From time to time, The Russian Women Network may be required to send you information about the service or your account. Except as mentioned above, The Russian Women Network will not send you unsolicited information, commercial offers or advertisements, including email. 

If at any time you believe that The Russian Women Network has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email at [ privacy@russian-women.net](mailto:privacy@russian-women.net?subject=%22Re:Privacy%22) and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem. 

For more information about our privacy statement, see the following Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs), or the FAQs accompanying The Russian Women Network site. If you have additional questions about this policy, please email us at [ privacy@russian-women.net](mailto:privacy@russian-women.net?subject=%22Re:Privacy%22)

## Frequently Asked Questions

**Qestion:** Do all The Russian Women Network services follow these privacy principles?   
**Answer:** Yes. The Russian Women Network privacy statement applies to those services that display this statement in conjunction with the Privacy Statement link on the site's Web pages. 

**Q:** How does The Russian Women Network use Personal Information?   
**A:** Usually, The Russian Women Network and our necessary service partners use your Personal Information to operate the site and to deliver their services. 

**Q:** Does The Russian Women Network share my Personal Information with other companies?   
**A:** The Russian Women Network does not share your Personal Information, except with partners who assist in providing services or products associated with The Russian Women Network site. 

In order to provide some of our services, The Russian Women Network may use partners and provide such partners with necessary Personal Information. Without this relationship, The Russian Women Network could not provide its service to you. 

Other companies may have access to your Personal Information to provide routine services, such as credit card processing, or may provide other essential elements of the site. 

**Q:** How do I correct or change Personal Information that I have given to The Russian Women Network?   
**A:** For all The Russian Women Network services, you can change your Personal Information through The Russian Women Network's [Account Infromation Page](http://www.russian-women.net/csedit.shtml)

Enter your email address and The Russian Women Network password, click the **[Edit Your Profile]** button. Change your information and click the **[Save Profile]** button. 

If you have difficulty modifying any of your information, please contact one of our member service representatives, [ customer_care@russian-women.net](mailto:customer_care@russian-women.net?subject=%22Re:AccountInfromation%22), and they will assist you in changing your information. 

**Q:** How does The Russian Women Network use the Personal Information (email address and postal address) you provide on the registration pages?   
**A:** We use your email address as your service username. We chose this since this ensures that everyone has a unique username and the username is easy to remember. We also use your email address to respond to incoming service requests from you. Because we service a lot of customers, email is the primary way we interact with our members. 

We ask for your postal address because some of our services, that a customer may choose, requires a mailing address so that we can completely perform the service. 

**Q:** Does The Russian Women Network have any links between the user's email address and their IP address record?   
**A:** Yes. Currently, we utilize this link to ensure better security for using our services. For example, when users try to log into our system, our authentication scheme does several checks to ensure the user is who they claim to be. One of these checks looks at the IP address to accurately identify The Russian Women Network member. 

**Q:** Does The Russian Women Network combine together Personal Information collected online with personal Information collected offline? If so, how is this information used by The Russian Women Network?   
**A:** No. Currently, The Russian Women Network does not collect any Personal Information through any means other than our website.
